http://www.dremu.com/privacy/

Privacy
Hi, I'm Julie Brumlik, owner of Dremu Skin Care. The privacy page is a lot of legal mumbo jumbo that is boring, but still important for you to understand. Let's cut to the chase. What most people want to know: Are you going to sell any information I give you to someone else to send me ads for something other than Dremu products? No. We hate spam and telemarketers as much as you do. The only thing you'll get from us is news about our products. And if you ever want to stop getting information from us, you can do that too. On every message you ever receive from us, there will be instructions on how to modify your notification preferences. Our feelings on the subject: If we treat you right, you'll come back. Welcome to the Dremu Family.
Dremu Skin Care Privacy Policy
When you provide us with information through Dremu Skin Care Online (the "Site"), we respect your privacy. It is important for you to understand what information we collect about you during your visit and what we do with that information. Your visit to the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions. Please note that this Privacy Policy governs only information provided to Dremu Skin Care Online and communications from Dremu Skin Care Online. It does not govern any other information or communications that may reference Dremu, e.g., communications from retailers or brick and mortar stores.
1. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information by Dremu Skin Care Online
We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you decide to complete an online survey, you may be asked to provide certain information such as your contact information (name, email address, mailing address, and telephone number), age group, gender and product and/or skin care concerns, and the brands and products you use. If you decide to place an order, we will also need to know your delivery and billing address, credit card number and expiration date. If you would prefer that we not collect any personally identifiable information from you, please do not provide us with any such information.
When you submit your personally identifiable information on the Site, you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.
2. Use of Personally Identifiable Information by Dremu Skin Care Online
a. Opt-In Communications
If you opt-in during the Site registration process or at other times when you submit personally identifiable information, the information you provide may be used by Dremu Skin Care Online to create and deliver to you our newsletters, surveys or other communications containing product information, skin care tips or promotions ("Opt-In Communications"). If you prefer not to receive such Opt-In Communications, please do not opt-in to receive these communications. If you do opt-in and later decide that you would no longer like to receive these communications, visit our Unsubscribe page.
b. Communications to Serve You
If you have elected to provide us with your contact information, e.g., by registering at the Site, emailing our Customer Service department or placing an order, we may provide you with service related announcements concerning the Site or contact you regarding your customer service requests or your order. For example, those visitors who have purchased a product will be notified by email about purchase and shipping information for their order. These types of communications are necessary to serve you, respond to your concerns and to provide the high level of customer service that Dremu Skin Care Online offers its customers.
3. No Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information for Third Party Marketing Without Your Consent
We will never provide your personally identifiable information to third parties for their use in marketing their products or services to you without your consent.
4. Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information
a. Fraud Protection and Compliance with Law
We may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. We may also exchange information, including personally identifiable information, with other companies and organizations for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.
b. Service Providers
We may retain other companies and individuals to perform functions consistent with our Privacy Policy on our behalf. Examples include customer support specialists, webhosting companies, fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that fill product orders or coordinate mailings), data analysis firms and email service providers. Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose.
c. Special Events
If you elect to participate in any promotions, sweepstakes, surveys, questionnaires or other events during your visit to our Site, the rules or terms and conditions for those events may indicate that your personally identifiable information will be shared with third parties. By choosing to participate and submitting your personally identifiable information with respect to such events, you consent to disclosure of your personally identifiable information to such third parties.
d. Business Transfers
As we continue to develop our business, we might sell certain of our assets. In such transactions, user information, including personally identifiable information, generally is one of the transferred business assets, and by submitting your personal information on the Site you agree that your data may be transferred to such parties in these circumstances.
5. Cookies and IP Addresses
A cookie is a piece of data that enables us to track and target your preferences. We may place a "cookie" on your computer's hard drive so we can recognize you as a return user and personalize your experience and your use of our Site. The cookie will be stored on your computer's hard drive until you remove it. We may also use temporary or "session" cookies to help you shop. These cookies will expire when you place an order. You can have your browser notify you of, or automatically reject, cookies. If you reject our cookies, you may still use the Site, but you may be limited in the use of some of the features. We may also use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track traffic patterns, and gather demographic information for aggregate use, as well as in combination with your personally identifiable information for credit fraud protection and risk reduction.
6. Pixel Tags and Tracking Technology
When you visit this Site or view one of our emails, we may use pixel tags (also called "clear" gifs), tracking links and/or similar technology to note some of the pages you visit on our Site and personalize your experience. We may also use pixel tags to determine what types of email your browser supports. We may use the information collected through pixel tags,tracking links and similar technology in combination with your personally identifiable information.
7. Use of Aggregate Information
We may use the information you provide in aggregate (non-personally identifiable) form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. We may collect, store or accumulate certain non-personally identifiable information concerning your use of the Site, such as information regarding which of our pages are most popular. We may share or transfer non-personally identifiable information with or to our affiliates, licensees and partners.
8. Children under 13
If you are under 13 years of age, you may browse our Site. However, you may not provide personal information to us. This Site is not designed for children and we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any children under 13.
9. Links
The Site may contain links to or from other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. This Privacy Policy applies only to the information we collect on the Site. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of other websites you link to from the Site or otherwise visit.
10. Shop securely online
At Dremu Skin Care Online we understand how important security is to you. When you place an order at Dremu Skin Care Online we encode your information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology. This is the most advanced consumer online security technique to date. You can be assured that your order will be placed safely and securely. We have used government approved encryption software. In order for encryption to take place, your browser must have the SSL protocol. The browsers that have this software are the following:
AOL 5.0 and higherInternet Explorer 5.0 and higherMozilla Firefox 1.0.4 (Windows only)Netscape 6.0 (Windows only)Safari
11. Notification of Changes
We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically consult this Privacy Policy. Please note that our rights to use your personally identifiable information will be based on the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is used.
12. Updating Your Information
You have the ability to review, change and/or correct the personally identifiable information you provide us by emailing us at help@dremu.com.
13. Choice/Opt-Out
You may opt-out of receiving future Opt-In Communications from Dremu Skin Care Online when you register at the Site or otherwise provide your contact information to Dremu Skin Care Online. You may opt out from written or email communication on our unsubscribe page.
14. Comments
We have taken great measures to ensure that your visit to the Site is an excellent one and that your privacy is constantly respected. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about the Site's privacy practices, please email us at help@dremu.com.
Copyright © 2006 Dremu. All rights reserved.
